KEVIN TUBBS

605 Angelica Ct Santa Teresa NM 88008 915-525-4250 (Cell) – KevinTubbs@ymail.com

Senior Director International Sales Development of International Sales in Africa and Europe from Russia

Program Manager

Lead an international team to develop and deliver a Telecommunications solution for delivery to customers in Europe, North America, and South America.

International Program Manager and Sales Executive with over 20 years experience leading successful programs and sales campaigns. Bilingual: English and Russian. Eight years of ex-pat experience living in Finland, France, and Russia. Strengths:

- **Leadership** Led a multi-national team in the development and total deployment of a Telecommunications solution with a multi-million dollar budget resulting in total sales of over \$50 million.
- **Team Building** Built a cohesive team across multiple continents that successfully delivered on-time and on-budget.
- Negotiator Directly negotiated product features and sales with the end customer
 in partnership with the sales team that resulted in new business and closed
 contracts.
- Customer Service / Customer Relations On the front line of customer service and support to ensure that all issues were resolved efficiently and to the customer's complete satisfaction.
- International Professional Experienced in living and working in multiple cultures on 4 continents (Europe, Africa, North America, and South America). Some familiarity, but not fluent, in French, Spanish, and Finnish.
- **Tools** Proficient with Microsoft Office, Microsoft Project, and contact management tools.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sales Management – CBOSS Association (2004-2007) 3 years experience in hiring, developing and managing an international sales team and working international exhibitions in order to build a sales channel in Africa.

KEVIN TUBBS

605 Angelica Ct Santa Teresa NM 88008 915-525-4250 (Cell) – KevinTubbs@ymail.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE - continued

Program Management – Hewlett Packard (1986 – 2004) 19 years of experience and training in Program management and key strategic customer account management. Most recently the International Telecommunication solutions program with successful deployment on 3 continents.

Customer Service – Tandem Computers (1993 – 1994) Director of Customer Support and Education responsible for 14 direct reports and all customer support and training issues.

Military Experience – U.S. Air Force (1972 – 1982) Honorable Discharge. Vietnam era veteran.

EDUCATION and TRAINING

- Corporate management and sales training from CBOSS and Hewlett Packard Company (HP).
- Progam and Project Management training from HP, Compaq, and Tandem Computers.
- Technical Sales and Support training from HP, Compaq, and Tandem Computers.
- U.S. Air Force Computer Programming Specialist on IBM and Honeywell mainframes.
- Defense Language Institute diploma Russian Language, 1973

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- **Fitness** Walking and light Gym work.
- Sport Golf
- **Investing** Personal
- Travel U.S. and International
- Languages Russian, Spanish, French, Finnish
- **Reading** Both Fiction and Non-Fiction